Secretary of the Faculty for Arts, Sciences and Engineering Records UA037
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject and Committee Files, 1858 -- 2015; 1945 -- 1999; UA037.002; 10.8 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s) 1,648 files; 344 Megabytes
  - Subject Files, 1858 -- 2006; UA037.002.001
    - Committee on Non - Tenured Faculty (Ad - Hoc), 1976; UA037.002.001.00017 (Box 1)
    - Committee on Scheduling and Registration, 1960 -- 1968; UA037.002.001.00018 (Box 1)
    - Committee on Student Life, 1971 -- 1972; UA037.002.001.00019 (Box 1)
    - Committee on Student Life, 1976 -- 1991; UA037.002.001.00020 (Box 1)
    - Committee on Student Organizations, 1954 -- 1965; UA037.002.001.00021 (Box 1)
    - Committee on Summer Research Fellowships, 1956 -- 1965; UA037.002.001.00022 (Box 1)
    - Committee on Tenure and Promotion, 1970 -- 1983; UA037.002.001.00023 (Box 1)
    - Committee on Values, 1941 -- 1943; UA037.002.001.00024 (Box 1)
    - [Curriculum Committee], 1966 -- 1983; UA037.002.001.00025 (Box 1)
    - [Curriculum Committee], 1959 -- 1966; UA037.002.001.00026 (Box 1)
    - [Curriculum Committee], 1954 -- 1959; UA037.002.001.00027 (Box 1)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1974 -- 1975; UA037.002.002.00001 (Box 2)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1974 -- 1975; UA037.002.002.00002 (Box 2)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1976; UA037.002.002.00003 (Box 2)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1975; UA037.002.002.00004 (Box 2)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1981 -- 1982; UA037.002.002.00005 (Box 2)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1981; UA037.002.002.00006 (Box 2)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1980 -- 1981; UA037.002.002.00007 (Box 2)
    - Curriculum Committee, Minutes and Recommendations to the Faculty and Reports of Action, 1983 -- 1984; UA037.002.002.00008 (Box 2)
    - Curriculum Committee, Minutes and Recommendations to the Faculty and Reports of Action, 1982 -- 1983; UA037.002.002.00009 (Box 2)
    - Curriculum Committee, Proposals, 1981 -- 1984; UA037.002.002.00010 (Box 2)
    - Curriculum Committee, Proposals, 1983; UA037.002.002.00011 (Box 2)
    - Curriculum Committee, Proposals, 1983; UA037.002.002.00012 (Box 2)
    - Curriculum Committee, Proposals, 1982; UA037.002.002.00013 (Box 2)
    - Curriculum Committee, Proposals, 1981 -- 1982; UA037.002.002.00014 (Box 2)
    - Curriculum Committee, Proposals, 1981; UA037.002.002.00015 (Box 2)
    - Curriculum Committee, Proposals, 1980 -- 1981; UA037.002.002.00016 (Box 2)
    - Educational Policy Committee (1), 1954 -- 1962; UA037.002.002.00017 (Box 2)
    - Educational Policy Committee (2), 1961 -- 1963; UA037.002.002.00018 (Box 2)
    - Educational Policy Committee (3), 1962 -- 1964; UA037.002.002.00019 (Box 2)
    - Educational Policy Committee (4), 1963 -- 1964; UA037.002.002.00020 (Box 2)
    - Educational Policy Committee (5), 1965 -- 1982; UA037.002.002.00021 (Box 2)
    - Enrollment, 1958 -- 1960; UA037.002.002.00022 (Box 2)
    - Faculty Club, 1951 -- 1978; UA037.002.002.00023 (Box 2)
    - General (1), 1858 -- 1989; UA037.002.002.00024 (Box 2)
    - General (2), 1955 -- 1980; UA037.002.002.00025 (Box 2)
    - Grievance Panel, 1982; UA037.002.002.00026 (Box 2)
    - Handbooks (1), 1949 -- 1980; UA037.002.002.00027 (Box 2)
    - Handbooks (2), 1970 -- 1985; UA037.002.003.00001 (Box 3)
    - [Handbooks], 1979; UA037.002.003.00002 (Box 3)
    - [Handbooks], 1983; UA037.002.003.00003 (Box 3)
    - [Handbooks], 1989; UA037.002.003.00004 (Box 3)
    - Orientation, 1975; UA037.002.003.00005 (Box 3)
    - Part-Time, 1972; UA037.002.003.00006 (Box 3)
    - Pension and Retirement, Carnegie Foundation, 1893 -- 1913; UA037.002.003.00007 (Box 3)
    - Pension and Retirement, Carnegie Foundation, 1916 -- 1919; UA037.002.003.00008 (Box 3)
    - Pension and Retirement, Carnegie Foundation, 1920 -- 1937; UA037.002.003.00009 (Box 3)
    - Pensions, Retirement, and Insurance, 1920 -- 1937; UA037.002.003.00010 (Box 3)
    - Pensions, Retirement, TIAA, 1920 -- 1978; UA037.002.003.00011 (Box 3)
    - Faculty - Photos, 1920 -- 1970; UA037.002.003.00012 (Box 3)
    - Sabbatical Leave, 1945 -- 1971; UA037.002.003.00013 (Box 3)
    - Salaries, 1971 -- 1977; UA037.002.003.00014 (Box 3)
    - Statistics: Minorities (Women), 1970 -- 1973; UA037.002.003.00015 (Box 3)
    - Summer Research: Correspondence, 1957 -- 1962; UA037.002.003.00016 (Box 3)
    - Summer Research Proposal (1958), UA037.002.003.00017 (Box 3)
    - Summer Research Proposal (1959), UA037.002.003.00018 (Box 3)
    - Summer Research Proposal (1960), UA037.002.003.00019 (Box 3)
    - Summer Research Proposal (1962), UA037.002.003.00020 (Box 3)
    - Summer Research Proposal (1963), UA037.002.003.00021 (Box 3)
    - Summer Research Proposal (1964), UA037.002.003.00022 (Box 3)
    - Summer Research Proposal (1965), UA037.002.003.00023 (Box 3)
    - Summer Research Proposal (1966), UA037.002.003.00024 (Box 3)
    - Summer Research Proposal (1967), UA037.002.003.00025 (Box 3)
    - Teacher's Oath, 1935 -- 1967; UA037.002.003.00026 (Box 3)
    - Tenure and Promotion Ad Hoc Committee, 1983 -- 1984; UA037.002.003.00027 (Box 3)
    - Workload Reports (1962-63) (1), 1962 -- 1963; UA037.002.003.00028 (Box 3)
    - Workload Reports (1962-63) (2), 1962 -- 1963; UA037.002.003.00029 (Box 3)
    - 40-40-20 Ad Hoc Comm, 1992 -- 1993; UA037.002.004.00001 (Box 4)
    - Academic Computing (Admin. Comm.), 1983 -- 1986; UA037.002.004.00002 (Box 4)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Fac Governance 1998-99, 1998 -- 1999; UA037.002.004.00003 (Box 4)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Faculty Retention, 2001; UA037.002.004.00004 (Box 4)
    - Admin Computer Usage and Facilities Comm, 1993; UA037.002.004.00005 (Box 4)
    - Administration and Governance Committee, 1979 -- 1981; UA037.002.004.00006 (Box 4)
    - ADV Comm on Fac Person (A and S Bylaw), 1971 -- 1983; UA037.002.004.00007 (Box 4)
    - Advising Task Force, 1990; UA037.002.004.00008 (Box 4)
    - Arena Summer Theater (Ad Hoc Comm), 1988 -- 1990; UA037.002.004.00009 (Box 4)
    - Arts Complex (Ad Hoc Comm), 1987 -- 1988; UA037.002.004.00010 (Box 4)
    - Biological Sciences (Ad Hoc Comm), 1976 -- 1977; UA037.002.004.00011 (Box 4)
    - Budget / Priorities, 87 - 87, 1985 -- 1989; UA037.002.004.00012 (Box 4)
    - Budget Priorites, 89 - 93 [1], 1992 -- 1993; UA037.002.004.00013 (Box 4)
    - Budget Priorites, 89 - 93 [2], 1990 -- 1992; UA037.002.004.00014 (Box 4)
    - Budget / Priorities and EPC Survey, 1984 -- 1987; UA037.002.004.00015 (Box 4)
    - Chairs'' Compensation Committee, 1999; UA037.002.004.00016 (Box 4)
    - Chair's Handbook, 1989; UA037.002.004.00017 (Box 4)
    - Chair's Taskforce, 1992 -- 1995; UA037.002.004.00018 (Box 4)
    - Committee on Joint Appts, 1987 -- 1988; UA037.002.004.00019 (Box 4)
    - Comm on Teaching, 1992 -- 1993; UA037.002.004.00020 (Box 4)
    - Committee on Undergrad Education, 1971 -- 1973; UA037.002.004.00021 (Box 4)
    - Computer Curriculum, 1983; UA037.002.004.00022 (Box 4)
    - Course Enrollment (Ad Hoc Comm), 1987 -- 1989; UA037.002.004.00023 (Box 4)
    - Curricula Comm (LA and J), (73 - 98) [1], 1990 -- 1997; UA037.002.004.00024 (Box 4)
    - Curricula Comm (LA and J), (73 - 98) [2], 1973 -- 1994; UA037.002.004.00025 (Box 4)
    - Diversity Comm., 1990; UA037.002.004.00026 (Box 4)
    - Educating Policy Comm., 1970 - 76, 1970 -- 1976; UA037.002.004.00027 (Box 4)
    - Educational Policy Committee, 1976-82, 1976 -- 1982; UA037.002.004.00028 (Box 4)
    - Educational Policy (Comm 1983 - 1995), UA037.002.004.00029 (Box 4)
    - Eight - Semester Rule, 1987 -- 1992; UA037.002.004.00030 (Box 4)
    - Emergency Action Comm (A and S Bylaw), 1983 -- 1994; UA037.002.004.00031 (Box 4)
    - Environmental Health and Safety, 1983 -- 1985; UA037.002.004.00032 (Box 4)
    - Faculty Appointment and Tenure Comm., 1981; UA037.002.004.00033 (Box 4)
    - Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual Task Force Report, 1993 -- 1994; UA037.002.004.00034 (Box 4)
    - Greek System [1], 1992 -- 1995; UA037.002.004.00035 (Box 4)
    - Greek System [2], 1992; UA037.002.004.00036 (Box 4)
    - Hydro - Quebec Committee, 1994; UA037.002.004.00037 (Box 4)
    - IACUC (Animal Care)[1], 1978 -- 1986; UA037.002.005.00001 (Box 5)
    - IACUC (Animal Care)[2], 1978 -- 1986; UA037.002.005.00002 (Box 5)
    - IACUC (Animal Care), 1987 -- 1988; UA037.002.005.00003 (Box 5)
    - IACUC (Animal Care) [1], 1989; UA037.002.005.00004 (Box 5)
    - IACUC (Animal Care) [2], 1989; UA037.002.005.00005 (Box 5)
    - IACUC (Animal Care), 1990; UA037.002.005.00006 (Box 5)
    - IACUC (Animal Care), 1991 -- 1992; UA037.002.005.00007 (Box 5)
    - Interdisciplinary Majors (LA and J Bylaw), 1988 -- 1995; UA037.002.005.00008 (Box 5)
    - International Scholarships and Fellowships, 1992 -- 1998; UA037.002.005.00009 (Box 5)
    - Investment Policies, 1978 -- 1988; UA037.002.005.00010 (Box 5)
    - Joint Committee on Teacher Education [1], 1998 -- 1999; UA037.002.005.00011 (Box 5)
    - Joint Committee on Teacher Education [2], 1999; UA037.002.005.00012 (Box 5)
    - Medford Master Planner Committee, 1984 -- 1986; UA037.002.005.00013 (Box 5)
    - Middle Manager's Group, 1990 -- 1992; UA037.002.005.00014 (Box 5)
    - Minor in ENGG Science, 1993; UA037.002.005.00015 (Box 5)
    - Minor's Program, 1980 -- 1984; UA037.002.005.00016 (Box 5)
    - Pre - Major Advising Task Force, 1991; UA037.002.005.00017 (Box 5)
    - Promotion and Prof. Task Force, 1994 -- 1995; UA037.002.005.00018 (Box 5)
    - Registration and Scheduling (A and S Bylaw), 1976 -- 2001; UA037.002.005.00019 (Box 5)
    - ROTC [1], 1981 -- 2004; UA037.002.005.00020 (Box 5)
    - ROTC [2], 1995 -- 1996; UA037.002.005.00021 (Box 5)
    - ROTC [3], 1995 -- 1996; UA037.002.005.00022 (Box 5)
    - Safety, 1993; UA037.002.005.00023 (Box 5)
    - Student Life (A and S By Law), 1973 -- 2006; UA037.002.005.00024 (Box 5)
    - Subcommittee on Tufts Programs Abroad, 2002; UA037.002.005.00025 (Box 5)
    - TA Task Force, 1993 -- 1994; UA037.002.005.00026 (Box 5)
    - Teacher Education, 1992; UA037.002.005.00027 (Box 5)
    - TEPC, 1993 -- 1995; UA037.002.005.00028 (Box 5)
    - Traffic Commission, 1997; UA037.002.005.00029 (Box 5)
    - Tufts Education Access TV Channel (ad hoc com), 1999; UA037.002.005.00030 (Box 5)
    - Tufts - Mus. School Affiliation Comm., 1996; UA037.002.005.00031 (Box 5)
    - Spring 2000 Classroom Media and Technology Committee, 1999 -- 2000; UA037.002.005.00032 (Box 5)
    - [University Wide Review of Graduate Programs, June 2001], 1993; UA037.002.005.00033 (Box 5)
    - Wright Center Advisory Committee, 1993; UA037.002.005.00034 (Box 5)
  - Committee files and Tenure and Promotion files, 1969 -- 2008; UA037.002.002
    - Archives committee [yellow], 1982 -- 1985; UA037.002.077.00001 (Box 77)
    - Benefits committee university wide [yellow], 1993 -- 1994; UA037.002.077.00002 (Box 77)
    - Bylaw committee [yellow], 2000; UA037.002.077.00003 (Box 77)
    - Campus planning and dev 80-81 to 99-00 [yellow] 1 of 2, 1980 -- 2000; UA037.002.077.00004 (Box 77)
    - Campus planning and dev 80-81 to 99-00 [yellow] 2 of 2, 1980 -- 2000; UA037.002.077.00005 (Box 77)
    - College writing subcommittee [yellow], 1990 -- 1999; UA037.002.077.00006 (Box 77)
    - Comm lists 69-70 to 93-94 [yellow] 1 of 2, 1969 -- 1994; UA037.002.077.00007 (Box 77)
    - Comm lists 69-70 to 93-94 [yellow] 2 of 2, 1969 -- 1994; UA037.002.077.00008 (Box 77)
    - Comm lists 94-95 to 03-04 [yellow] 1 of 2, 1994 -- 2004; UA037.002.077.00009 (Box 77)
    - Comm lists 94-95 to 03-04 [yellow] 2 of 2, 1994 -- 2004; UA037.002.077.00010 (Box 77)
    - Continuing educ advisory comm [yellow], 1995 -- 2005; UA037.002.077.00011 (Box 77)
    - Computer facilities and uses (A&S) [yellow], 1982 -- 1991; UA037.002.077.00012 (Box 77)
    - Curr. review comm (Blue Sky Comm) [yellow], 1975 -- 1992; UA037.002.077.00013 (Box 77)
    - Distribution requirement (LA and J Bylaw) [yellow], 1991 -- 2001; UA037.002.077.00014 (Box 77)
    - Editorial comm [yellow], 1994 -- 1995; UA037.002.077.00015 (Box 77)
    - Educational policy 71-72 to 99-00 [yellow], 1971 -- 2000; UA037.002.077.00016 (Box 77)
    - EPPIC Advisory board [yellow], 1995 -- 2006; UA037.002.077.00017 (Box 77)
    - Environmental studies [yellow], 1992 -- 1998; UA037.002.077.00018 (Box 77)
    - Experimental college board (A&S) [yellow], 1983 -- 2002; UA037.002.077.00019 (Box 77)
    - Faculty liason commm A&S Fac Mtg-A&S bylaw [yellow] 1 of 2, 1991 -- 2005; UA037.002.077.00020 (Box 77)
    - Faculty liason commm A&S Fac Mtg-A&S bylaw [yellow] 2 of 2, 1983 -- 1991; UA037.002.077.00021 (Box 77)
    - Foreign lang/cultures requirement subcomm LA&J [yellow], 1988 -- 2002; UA037.002.077.00022 (Box 77)
    - Honors committee [yellow], 1974 -- 1986; UA037.002.077.00023 (Box 77)
    - Institutional policy (ad hoc comm) [yellow], 1987 -- 2004; UA037.002.077.00024 (Box 77)
    - Lang and culture comm (A&S ad hoc) [yellow], 2004 -- 2006; UA037.002.077.00025 (Box 77)
    - Legal review of T&P procedures 6/98 [yellow], 1998; UA037.002.077.00026 (Box 77)
    - Nat'l and Int'l scholar awards (A&S) [yellow], 1985 -- 1997; UA037.002.077.00027 (Box 77)
    - Oversight committee for continuing ed. [yellow], 1995; UA037.002.077.00028 (Box 77)
    - Plans of study (LA and J bylaw) [yellow], 1989 -- 2008; UA037.002.077.00029 (Box 77)
    - Policy and programs (GS bylaw) [yellow], 1969 -- 1998; UA037.002.077.00030 (Box 77)
    - Post retirement health rev. committee [yellow], 1992; UA037.002.077.00031 (Box 77)
    - Salaries corollaries and benefits[yellow], 1997 -- 2002; UA037.002.077.00032 (Box 77)
    - Review of faculty bylaws (ad hoc comm) [yellow], 1982 -- 1992; UA037.002.077.00033 (Box 77)
    - Social - frat and sor life (A&S) [yellow], 1988 -- 1996; UA037.002.078.00001 (Box 78)
    - Specific learning dis (A&S bylaw) [yellow], 1989 -- 2003; UA037.002.078.00002 (Box 78)
    - Ad hoc T&P comm [green], 1975 -- 1996; UA037.002.078.00003 (Box 78)
    - T&P ad hoc committee reports [green], 1979 -- 1997; UA037.002.078.00004 (Box 78)
    - T&P general info [green] 1 of 2, 1969 -- 1980; UA037.002.078.00005 (Box 78)
    - T&P general info [green] 2 of 2, 1969 -- 1980; UA037.002.078.00006 (Box 78)
    - T&P general info [green] 1 of 2, 1980 -- 1986; UA037.002.078.00007 (Box 78)
    - T&P general info [green] 2 of 2, 1980 -- 1986; UA037.002.078.00008 (Box 78)
    - T&P general info [green], 1986 -- 1990; UA037.002.078.00009 (Box 78)
    - T&P general info [green], 1990 -- 2001; UA037.002.078.00010 (Box 78)
    - Undergrad advising and counseling (A&S) [yellow], 1977 -- 2006; UA037.002.078.00011 (Box 78)
    - University art collection [yellow], 1983 -- 2006; UA037.002.078.00012 (Box 78)
    - Web editorial board [yellow], 1996; UA037.002.078.00013 (Box 78)
    - World civ program [yellow] 1 of 2, 1991 -- 2005; UA037.002.078.00014 (Box 78)
    - World civ program [yellow] 2 of 2, 1986 -- 2002; UA037.002.078.00015 (Box 78)
    - Writing across the curriculum [yellow] 1 of 2, 1985 -- 1995; UA037.002.078.00016 (Box 78)
    - Writing across the curriculum [yellow] 2 of 2, 1988 -- 1992; UA037.002.078.00017 (Box 78)
  - FRAC, 2007 -- 2009; UA037.002.082.00001 (Box 82)
  - FRF Fall, 2007; UA037.002.082.00002 (Box 82)
  - FRF Spring, 2008; UA037.002.082.00003 (Box 82)
  - FRF Fall, 2008; UA037.002.082.00004 (Box 82)
  - FRF Spring, 2009; UA037.002.082.00005 (Box 82)
  - FRF Fall, 2009; UA037.002.082.00006 (Box 82)
  - Senior Research Fellowship Fall, 2007; UA037.002.082.00007 (Box 82)
  - Senior Semester Fellowship Fall, 2008; UA037.002.082.00008 (Box 82)
  - Summer Faculty Fellowship Fall, 2007; UA037.002.082.00009 (Box 82)
  - Summer Faculty Fellowship Fall, 2008; UA037.002.082.00010 (Box 82)
  - New Direction Fall, 2007; UA037.002.082.00011 (Box 82)
  - New Direction Spring, 2008; UA037.002.082.00012 (Box 82)
  - New Direction Award Fall, 2008; UA037.002.082.00013 (Box 82)
  - Distinguished Scholar Spring, 2008; UA037.002.082.00014 (Box 82)
  - Distinguished Scholar Award Spring, 2009; UA037.002.082.00015 (Box 82)
  - GIAs Fall, 2007; UA037.002.082.00016 (Box 82)
  - GIAs Spring, 2008; UA037.002.082.00017 (Box 82)
  - GIAS Fall, 2008; UA037.002.082.00018 (Box 82)
  - GIAS Spring, 2009; UA037.002.082.00019 (Box 82)
  - FRAC, 2010 -- 2011; UA037.002.082.00020 (Box 82)
  - FRF Spring, 2010; UA037.002.082.00021 (Box 82)
  - FRF Fall, 2010; UA037.002.082.00022 (Box 82)
  - FRF Spring, 2011; UA037.002.082.00023 (Box 82)
  - Senior and Mellon Leaves Fall, 2009; UA037.002.083.00001 (Box 83)
  - Senior & Mellon Leaves Fall, 2010; UA037.002.083.00002 (Box 83)
  - Summer Faculty Fellowship Fall, 2009; UA037.002.083.00003 (Box 83)
  - Summer Faculty Fellowship Fall, 2010; UA037.002.083.00004 (Box 83)
  - New Directions Award Fall, 2009; UA037.002.083.00005 (Box 83)
  - New Directions Spring, 2010; UA037.002.083.00006 (Box 83)
  - Distinguished Scholar Spring, 2010; UA037.002.083.00007 (Box 83)
  - Distinguished Scholar Award Spring, 2011; UA037.002.083.00008 (Box 83)
  - GIAS Fall, 2009; UA037.002.083.00009 (Box 83)
  - GIAS Spring, 2010; UA037.002.083.00010 (Box 83)
  - GIAS Fall, 2010; UA037.002.083.00011 (Box 83)
  - GIAS Spring, 2011; UA037.002.083.00012 (Box 83)
  - FRF Fall, 2011; UA037.002.083.00013 (Box 83)
  - FRF Spring, 2012; UA037.002.083.00014 (Box 83)
  - FRF Fall, 2012; UA037.002.083.00015 (Box 83)
  - FRF Spring, 2013; UA037.002.083.00016 (Box 83)
  - Mellon Proposals, 2012 -- 2013; UA037.002.083.00017 (Box 83)
  - Senior Semester Leave, 2011 -- 2012; UA037.002.083.00018 (Box 83)
  - Senior Semester Leave, 2012 -- 2013; UA037.002.083.00019 (Box 83)
  - Summer Fellowship, 2011 -- 2012; UA037.002.083.00020 (Box 83)
  - Summer Fellowship, 2012 -- 2013; UA037.002.083.00021 (Box 83)
  - Distinguished Scholar Award, 2011 -- 2012; UA037.002.083.00022 (Box 83)
  - Distinguished Scholar Award, 2012 -- 2013; UA037.002.083.00023 (Box 83)
  - GIA, 2011 -- 2012; UA037.002.083.00024 (Box 83)
  - GIA, 2012 -- 2013; UA037.002.083.00025 (Box 83)
  - Faculty Research Awards Committee files, 2012 -- 2015; UA037.002.083.00026; 1 Digital Object(s) 1,648 files; 344 Megabytes
    Includes proposals, lists of awards, and reports.
- Official papers, 1896 -- 1946; UA037.003; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series consists of materials found uncatalogued in the stacks in July, 2007. Committee reports, correspondence, and memos were pasted into metal post binders. DCA staff removed materials from binders during processing. Provenance is unknown. Notes on the materials indicate that they were microfilmed at one time.
  - Official papers (Faculty) Volume I [Binder] 1 of 3, 1896 -- 1905; UA037.003.075.00001 (Box 75)
  - Official papers (Faculty) Volume I [Binder] 2 of 3, 1896 -- 1905; UA037.003.075.00002 (Box 75)
  - Official papers (Faculty) Volume I [Binder] 3 of 3, 1896 -- 1905; UA037.003.075.00003 (Box 75)
  - Official papers (Faculty) Volume II [Binder] 1 of 2, 1905 -- 1909; UA037.003.075.00004 (Box 75)
  - Official papers (Faculty) Volume II [Binder] 2 of 2, 1905 -- 1909; UA037.003.075.00005 (Box 75)
  - Official papers (Faculty) Volume III [Binder] 1 of 1, 1909 -- 1913; UA037.003.075.00006 (Box 75)
  - Official papers (Faculty) Volume IV [Binder] 1 of 2, 1913 -- 1918; UA037.003.075.00007 (Box 75)
  - Official papers (Faculty) Volume IV [Binder] 2 of 2, 1913 -- 1918; UA037.003.075.00008 (Box 75)
  - Official papers (Faculty) Volume V [Binder] 1 of 1, 1918 -- 1923; UA037.003.075.00009 (Box 75)
  - Official papers (Faculty) Volume VI [Binder] 1 of 1, 1921 -- 1927; UA037.003.075.00010 (Box 75)
  - Official papers (Faculty) Volume VII [Binder] 1 of 2, 1928 -- 1946; UA037.003.075.00011 (Box 75)
  - Official papers (Faculty) Volume VII [Binder] 2 of 2, 1928 -- 1946; UA037.003.075.00012 (Box 75)
- Additional accessions, 1988 -- 2014; UA037.004; 1.2 Linear Feet
  GSAS faculty meeting minutes, 1988-2005.
  - GSAS faculty meeting minutes; FRAC files, 1988 -- 2014; UA037-001 (Box data_value_missing_ebf31ad46f109bdaace1e62115794576, Box 1)
    GSAS faculty meeting minutes, 1988-2005; FRAC files, 2013-2014